Why all the sudden the change of heart?
为什么突然改主意了？
Because a cop is down...
因为一个警察已经死了
Then you can help...
那你能帮忙了
You're the only one I'll let her talk to...
我只同意你跟她谈
She saw it all...
她什么都看到了
One Adam 18, Alameda and 11th...
1-A-18, 拉么达街和11街交界
ETA, 12 minutes...
12分钟后到
Bill!
比尔！
Jesus Christ Bill... Get back here...
回来！
The bomb squad's on the way...
爆破队已经在路上了
I got a guyon the cell phone, tells me she's got the whole story...
电话上的人告诉我 那个女的知道整个事情
Son of a bitch...
混蛋
Wait until he gets back here...
那等他回来再说
No one... not you, not us... goes over there...
谁都不能过去
I swear to God I'll take you down, Bill...
我会逮捕你的，比尔
Now get back here...
马上回来
Welcome to our party...
欢迎加入我们
We're conferenced...
我们联在一起了
A-team, Liberty Wallace,
A 队, 丽柏蒂 华莱士,
please let me introduce you to Bill Tollman...
我来给你介绍比尔
We're lucky to have Bill join us...
很幸运比尔能加入我们
He's ambitious, smart, and for the most part...
他有野心，很精明 但更重要的是
honest...
诚实
I'm sorry...
很抱歉
And you are?
那你是谁
I'm Joe... I'm out for vengeance...
我是乔 我要报仇
Liberty needs forgiveness...
丽柏蒂 需要宽恕
And we both need publicity...
而你我都需要
Why me?
为什么找我
Your lucky day...
你的幸运日
Why don't you bring him up to speed, Liberty?
丽柏蒂 ,跟他讲讲怎么回事
He's got a military-issue, sniper rifle pointed right at you...
他有一个部队专用的狙击枪瞄着你
He's an ex cellent shot...
他很准的
There's a bomb in the hot dog cart...
在那个卖热狗的车里有颗炸弹
It's set to blow, if my cell phone battery dies, for any reason...
如果我的手机没电了， 炸弹就会爆炸
The bomb's big enough to blow up this entire block...
这颗炸弹足可炸毁整个街段
Think Oklahoma...
想想那次奥克拉荷马的爆炸
That theater's going to let out in less than an hour...
戏院还有30分钟就散场了
I have less than an hour left on my battery...
我的手机电池还可持续不到一个钟头
I die either way...
我是必死了
Unless you get out of here soon, so do you...
除非你马上离开，否则你也会死
Aren't you the Liberty Wallace of...
你就是那个丽柏蒂 华莱士
Yes...
我是
Any demands?
有什么要求
He wants...
他想
He wants somebody to pay for the death of his daughter...
他想找人给他女儿偿命
Almost right...
意思差不多
Joe's daughter, died...
乔的女儿死了
from a fucked up kid with a gun...
被一个孩子用枪打死的
It was a gun manufactured by my company...
那把枪是我们公司造的
He wants me to die, knowing I have blood on my hands...
他想让我死， 因为我手上沾满了血
Joe, you've got to rethink here...
乔，你要三思
This is crazy...
这是很愚蠢的
There's a real gun pointed at you...
比尔，他真有枪对着你
What I mean is, there are other ways,
我的意思是， 还有其他解决方法
Uh-huh...
是啊
That's where you come in, Bill...
所以把你找来
You want me to use my influence as a journalist,
你要用我记者的影响
to debate the right to bear arms with you,
去跟你辩论是否可以带枪
because you've got a gun pointed at me?
因为你拿枪对着我
I'm standing next to a bomb that's on final countdown...
我呢，却站在定时炸弹旁
Yeah...
没错
What happens when all this is over?
等这一切都完了，会怎样
I blow my brains out...
我会自杀
This becomes my journalistic moment of truth...
这是我记者生涯就关键的时刻
Your Emmy...
你的艾美奖
And your quest...
和你的探索
I'm sorry, Joe... What do you want me to say here?
对不起，乔，那你让我说什么
Say yes...
说是
No... Say that you're accountable...
不 说你靠得住
Say yes...
说是
There are plenty of causes, Joe...
乔，还有很多其他原因
Bill, look at Liberty...
比尔，看着 丽柏蒂...
She's going to die...
她很快就会死
It's her choice when,
她选择时间
it's my choice how...
我选择方式
You have a similar dilemma...
你们身处同样困境
Now,
现在
Iook around...
回头看看
Jesus, shit...
天哪...
He shot me...
他打中我了
I'll do whatever he wants...
他让我干什么都行
He's going to die in your arms, Liberty...
他会在你怀里死去, 丽柏蒂
Get ready...
准备好了
Watching someone die...
眼怔怔看着一个人死去
changes you forever...
会改变你一生
19-86...
19-86
to Dispatch... We have a female with a gun...
总部 这里有一个持枪的女士
I'm not dying...
我不要死
His father is Senator Robert Tollman...
他父亲是参议员罗伯特
He's also a constitutional lawyer...
他还是立宪律师
He lobbied for the NRA,
他还为国家步枪协会游说过
so we know which side his bread is buttered on...
我们知道他是站在哪边的
He's proud of his son...
他为他儿子自豪
And now like me,
但现在，他和我一样
has every reason to switch sides...
有所有的理由改变立场
Hey...
嘿
How many times do I have to tell you?
我要跟你说多少次
Turn that fucking thing off...
把它关掉
Just hang on... Help's coming...
坚持住 有人来救你
No... It's not...
不， 不会来的
- Fucking asshole... - Sue me...
- 他妈的王八蛋 - 去告我啊
Get him out of here...
把他赶走
Can't buy this kind of press...
不能买这种报社的报纸...
10:00 news, buddy...
10点新闻，哥们
Call my father for me...
给我父亲打电话
Why are you doing this?
你为什么要这么做
Why?
为什么
Tell me...
告诉我
Your dick is the size of the little trigger on that gun...
你根本不算是个男人
That makes you nothing, Joe...
乔，你什么都不是
You're less than nothing...
你什么都不如
You probably didn't even have a daughter,
你可能连女儿都没用
if you did, she's better off dead...
如果你有女儿， 那她死了最好
I'll forgive you for that,
我原谅你说的话
given the circumstances...
这样的话
Just kill me...
干脆把我杀了
- Get it over with... - Shut up...
- 早杀，事早了结 - 闭嘴
I'm not the one shooting...
不是我开的枪
I can't take anymore...
我受不了了
I'm going to hang up...
我马上就把电话挂了
That asshole's shooting with a... 9 millimeter,
那个王八蛋 用的是9毫米口径的枪
He hasn't got a hope of hitting you from that distance...
他在那么远处打你，想都别想
Ah, Victor...
啊, 维克托...
You have made my day...
你完蛋了
Hello...
喂
It's kind of ironic,
真是讽刺
me saving your life...
我救了你的命
They're here...
他们来了
The officer went down over there...
警察是在那边被击中的
The lady with the bomb is across the street...
那个带着炸弹的女的 在马路对面
It's time to do something...
该行动了
Bill has a tape recorder, in his suit pocket...
在比尔的西服兜里有个录音机
Name names, Liberty...
丽柏蒂，告诉我名字
Blow the lobbies wide open...
把那些丑闻都斗出来
Payoffs are always good news breakers...
贪污受贿一贯是很好的新闻
You're an amateur, Joe...
乔，你是个业余的
No... No... No... Don't tell me that you're worried about the fallout...
不，不，不， 不要告诉我你会担心结果
Your husband, or someone he works for,
你丈夫或他上司
has or dered the CIA thugs to put a bullet in you...
下了命令要杀了你
Is that the world you want to live in?
你想活在那样的世界里吗
What do you think you can accomplish
你想只是纸上谈兵
by me babbling about Senator-this and Senator-that?
就能解决问题吗
That's not going to do anything...
什么事都解决不了
It's a start...
是个开始
It's an end, Joe...
是结尾，乔
Let me do what I can really do...
让我做我力所能及的
Let me work from the inside...
让我从内部开始
I can...
我能
I can do something...
我真的能做
So that's what you tell yourself every morning?
你每天早上都对自己说这些吗
Joe, I can really change things...
乔，我真能改变一些事的
I promise you I'll do it...
我向你保证，我一定行
I promise...
我保证
Police... Put them down...
我是警察，把枪放下
Come on...
走开
We can always count on our nation's finest to serve and protect...
我们可以永远依赖警察来保护
Shots fired... I've got a civilian down possibly dead...
开枪了 我这有个市民可能死了
Looks like a shooter...
看起来好像是个射手
Senator Libby
参议员 利比
took at least three payments in cash...
收了至少3次现金付款
Senator Lipton, Crick, Congressmen Gomez...
参议员 利普顿,和 克里克, 国会议员 宫...
Check Geneva bank accounts,
去查日内瓦银行帐户
Swiss Union bank accounts,
瑞士银行帐户
Cayman Islands, Bahamas...
凯门岛，巴哈马群岛
My husband...
我丈夫
Victor Wallace is fucking the president's wife,
维克托华莱士和总统夫人有一手
among others...
还有其他人
Presidents...
总统
or wives?
还是夫人
Humph...
呲
What do you want me to do?
你让我怎么做
Nothing... You're on a roll...
没别的事 你现在做的很好
Keep it going...
继续讲啊
You're already on the news...
你已经上新闻了
Victor's mobilized every senator I've just mentioned...
维克托已经吩咐我刚刚说过的几个参议员行动了
The police chief is in his back pocket...
警察局长也是他的人
He supplies the gang that controls this corner, for Christ's sake...
他还给当地黑帮提供枪支
He?
他？
Okay... I...
还有我
We...
我们
I...
我
I'm in this, okay?
我也参与了
Is that what you want me to say, "I'm in it"?
你想听到我也参与了，对吧？
Yes...
对
Now, who are you going to trust?
现在你能相信谁？
Nobody...
无人可信
- Keep talking... - No...
- 继续说 - 不
I'll name names, I'll bury everyone who deserves it,
我可以继续说下去
but you have to shut this bomb off...
但是你必须先把炸弹拆掉
Uhh... can't...
不可能
Then I can't...
那我也不能说了
Fair enough...
好啊，很合理
You've done your job anyway...
反正你已经做了该做的了
Now we can depend on Bill's dad, the senator,
现在我们可以利用比尔的父亲
and his newfound quest...
来完成此事
He'll go down as a hero for the cause...
他会光荣的死去
It was a life well spent...
从大局来看
In the big picture...
他会死的很值
Have a hot dog...
吃个热狗吧
You don't want to go out on an empty stomach...
不能饿着肚子干事
Let them take him away...
让他们把他抬走吧
Ma'am...
小姐
Come with me, ma'am...
请跟我来
Over here...
到这边来
Woman: Every Thursday,
每周四
they meet backstage,
他们都会在后台见面
go into Russell's dressing room, and lock the door...
然后一起去拉塞尔的更衣室， 再锁上门
They order in...
他们一起吃外卖
Bastard changed the lock...
混蛋把锁给换了
Fuck...
他妈的
Yeah, she slinks out sometime during the night,
她有时到晚上会偷偷的出去
and we don't see Russell again until the next performance...
我们要等到下次表演才会再看到拉塞尔
Oh... Ex cept for tonight...
对了，除了今晚
He's probably in there, fucked to death...
他可能还在里面
Uh-oh...
噢
Time to call a locksmith...
那该叫个锁匠来
Back up's coming in from 53...
后援马上就到
Look's like we've got ourselves a sniper...
看起来是有个狙击手
There's no I... D... on the woman,
那个女的没有身份证
no trace on her cell phone yet...
她手机也是毫无线索
If she's chained to the stand...
她可能是被锁在那里
She told officers there was a bomb, all right?
她还告诉警察那有颗炸弹 明白了？
We believe she's working with the sniper...
我们认为她和那个狙击手是一伙的
The man on the ground out there, is a reporter with KNBS...
躺在地上的男子是个记者
Bill Tollman, the senator's son...
比尔 托曼, 是个参议员的儿子
We believe shot...
应该是被击中的
We have a confirmed fatality in a parking structure back here...
已有一人在我们背后的停车处被杀
We don't have enough information on that yet,
但还没用足够的资料
but we can't rule out terrorists, militia, or just a basic nutcase...
可能是恐怖份子，或部队的 要么就是个神经病
We're going to block 5th to 10th, Olive to Berry...
现在要把周围的街道全部封锁
We've got at least 20 buildings to evacuate...
我们至少要疏散这20栋楼
We're thin on manpower...
但是我们人手不够
Use uniforms to back you up...
要用民警帮忙
All right? Be safe, gentlemen... Let's go...
听懂了？ 好，注意安全。  出发！
Swat member: Captain...
队长
We've got no location on the shooter,
我们还不知道射手在哪儿
No I... D... on the woman... We've got backup coming in...
还是不知道那女的是谁 后援已经到了
We're set up in the garage back here...
我们已经在后方停车场设置好了
Somebody shut them down... Jesus...
找人把他们赶走
Clear the media back, please...
请把记者都赶走
We are live...
现在是现场直播
The drama continues in downtown LA,
在洛杉矶市中心
where we apparently have a fatal shooting of an officer,
有人持枪打死了一位民警
here at the corner of Grace and 9th...
在这个十字路口
Is your wife going to be tuning in?
你老婆会在看这条新闻吗？
No...
不会
But I guarantee your husband's watching...
但我敢说你老公肯定会在看
Back to you, Dennis...
到你了，丹尼思
My husband...
我老公
My husband's on the way to the airport by now...
他已经在去飞机场的路上了
He will be unreachable for comment...
他们找不到他来评论此事
Why'd you marry him?
你为什么和他结婚？
I thought he could save my father's company...
我本以为他能挽救我父亲的公司
It was a bad idea...
不是个明智的选择
I even thought I loved him...
我甚至以为我爱上他了
Should we do a shield rescue for the guyon the ground?
我们要不要去把那个男的救过来
No... It's too risky until we find out where the shooter is...
不行，太危险。 等找到狙击手再说吧
Poor bastard's gonna bleed out...
可怜他会流血致死
I want all traffic locked down
我要封锁这里所有交通
from 5th to 9th...
从第5街到第9街
Yeah, that's done already...
是，已经做好了
Who's the negotiator on call?
谁去交涉？
John's going to be here in 10 minutes, Captain...
队长，约翰10分钟内就到
Joe, more death isn't going to make the guns disappear,
乔，更多的死伤不会让枪支消失的
it's not going to bring your daughter back...
也同样不会把你女儿救活
I'm begging you...
我求求你
Oh... Liberty...
噢，丽柏蒂...
Tiananmen Square boiled down to one man,
记得当年在天安门广场
standing in front of a tank, that couldn't move or shoot...
剩下一个人站在坦克前 连坦克拿他都没办法
Because human dignity was stronger
因为人的尊严
than steel or bullets...
比钢铁、子弹还要坚固
It changed a nation...
那件事改变了一个国家
That was a completely different situation...
这两件事根本不一样
What's the difference?
有什么不一样？
We've got gated communities,
我们有关闭式的社区和警报系统
security systems, and kids carrying combat weapons,
小孩子能拿到武器
all because most people
这全是因为
haven't even read the 2nd amendment...
许多人根本没读过第二修正案
So,
所以
our freedom of speech,
只要我们不去惹有枪的人
is protected,
我们的言论自由
as long as we don't piss off a guy with a gun...
就会受到保护
I'm not brave enough to take a bullet for my country...
我没用勇气去前线
You underestimate yourself...
你低估了自己
The one thing that guarantees our freedom,
唯一可以保障我们的自由
and independence, is responsibility...
是责任感
We lost that somewhere between Vietnam and presidential blowjobs...
但是我们已经失去了
Manyof the Fathers of the Constitution...
很多编写我国宪法的前辈们
had slaves, but they wrote a document,
都有奴隶在家
about freedom...
但他们居然还写个关于自由的文件
Go figure...
好好想想吧
So you see, things are meant to change...
所以，很多事是注定要改的
We're all grown up now...
现在我们都是成年人了
So are you, Liberty...
丽柏蒂， 你也是
I think you've figured out
我想你应该想通了
there's no such thing
这世上根本没用
as a politically correct gun...
政治上来说合法的枪
I'll say all that to the press...
这些我都会对媒体说的
But please turn this bomb off, Joe...
乔，请把炸弹拆掉吧
I don't know what to do next...
我不知道接下来该怎么办
It feels like this whole thing was a dream...
觉得好像是在做一个梦
I should have told you before, but I...
我在之前就应该跟你说，但是我
What do we do now?
我们现在要怎么做
Huh...
哼
The cops have...
那些警察带了一些
G-36's...
G-36式步枪
Did you make that deal too?
也是你卖的吧？
It was more of a donation...
说捐献跟准确些
I'll bet that you were a hero...
我想你对他们来说算个英雄
We got a big luncheon,
我们参加了个很多的午宴
key to the city, mayor in my pocket,
被奖励了城市的钥匙 市长也站在我们这边
- You make it sound so easy... - If you've got the cash flow,
- 听起来是轻而易举的事 - 如果你有钱的话
a little planning goes a long way...
事半功倍...
Did they know you had just sold 26 stripped down
他们知不知道你卖的
P-99's that went straight to the streets?
那26把P-99式手枪直接进了黑市
I guess it was one of those an-eye-for-an-eye deals...
我想那可能是宗“以眼换眼”的生意
It's easy to get lost in a deal...
良心也拿来交易了...
I know it's not an ex cuse...
我知道那不是借口
This is a perfect fucking nightmare...
真他妈的可怕
127 locations for an asshole with a gun...
狙击手有127个藏身处
We've got a cell phone we can't bust into,
从手机上又找不出任何线索
and a bomb next to a theater...
戏院旁还有颗炸弹
Anybody picking up in there yet?
有人接电话吗？
- Just voicemail... - Fucking voicemail...
- 只有留言机 - 他妈的留言机
Well...
好啊
the shooter is back...
那个射手回来了
Who's he work for?
他为谁效力？
Your husband or the CIA?
你老公还是中央情报局?
Whoever's got the cash...
他为钱效力
Who's the cowboy in the chopper?
谁在直升机里？
Get him higher, he's surveillance...
再升高点 他替我们监视整个地区
I don't want him landing on the fucking rooftop...
我可不想他从房顶落下来
Okay, you guys, let's get in here...
好了，我们行动吧
Let's get into the theater...
我们进戏院
I should have told you before, but I...
我之前就应该告诉你，但我...
What do we do now?
我们怎么办
It's up to you...
你决定
Do you still love me?
你还爱我吗？
Of course I do...
当然爱你
How about you?
你呢？
Of course...
当然啦
It won't make a bit of difference...
这是什么都改变不了的
How full is the theater?
戏院里有多少人？
It's the last performance...
这是最后一场演出
I figure 10 to clear the building,
我想大概要10分钟清场
Copy that... No one exits the front door...
收到 谁都别从前门出去
Hold until we've cleared all rear exits...
等我们把好后门再走
Senator Tollman's son was just shot,
扣押丽柏蒂的人
by the same guy who's got Liberty...
已经把参议员托曼的儿子打伤
I'm calling your husband...
我给你老公打电话
Why?
为什么
Yeah...
什么事
Who called the militia?
谁调动的部队？
I want to talk to Liberty...
我要和丽柏蒂讲话
Touching...
感人啊
It's not one of yours?
这么说不是你的人喽？
That's not good, Victor...
那可不好办了，维克托
Liberty are you there?
丽柏蒂 你在吗？
Such a sweet name, don't you think?
多好听的名字，你觉得呢
Her parents were Republican...
她父母都是共和党的
I want to talk to my wife...
我要和我老婆讲话
I'm here...
我在这
Alive...
还活着
And on TV...
也在电视上
I... uh...
我...
I know, you're doing what you have to do...
我知道你会做你必须做的事
You know who's calling the shots?
你知道谁在主持这一切？
The president's wife?
总统夫人？
Come on...
你知道不是的
No, of course not... If it were, you'd be standing here...
对，当然不是她 如果是她，那就会是你站在这儿了
I'm doing what I can, but...
我会想尽一切办法
You know the rules, right?
但是你是知道游戏规则的，对吧？
Aw, honey,
噢，亲爱的
fuck you...
去你的吧
Joe, hang up...
乔，把电话挂掉
No, what she meant is,
不，我想她是说
why don't you let her die with some dignity?
你让她死得有些尊严
Get the car...
去把车开过来
- Mr... Wallace is leaving... - Yes, sir...
- 华莱士 先生要走 - 是
Right through here... Right this way...
从这边走
Through here...
从这过去
How do you know Victor?
你怎么认识维克托的？
Classified...
这是机密
Keep moving this way... Come on, let's go!
继续向前走 快走  快点
- Copy that... - Who the fuck is she?
- 收到了 - 她到底是谁？
We just I... D... 'd her, Liberty Wallace...
刚刚差到，她就是丽柏蒂 华莱士
the VP of McCloud, married to the CEO,
是McCloud 公司的副总裁 总裁是她老公
connections up the wazoo...
跟多方面都有关系
Jesus Christ... I know him... Victor...
我的天啊 我认识他...是维克托
Yeah, we're trying to track him down right now...
对，我们现在正在找他
Then there's no way she's with the shooter, she's a hostage...
她决不可能和那个射手是一伙的
So I'm bait...
那我做诱饵
No, more like...
不对
more like a showpiece...
应该是展览品
I like your reckless side...
我喜欢你有时粗心
You travel without your body guard,
每周至少有5个小时
five hours every week and sometimes twice...
出门不带保镖
You're a little bit more accessible and predictable
你比总统夫人
than the president's wife...
更容易接近
So, who's pissed off at Victor, the president?
维克托把谁给惹恼了？ 总统？
No...
错了
It's all me this time...
这次是我个人的主意
I was a dad...
我以前还是个父亲
I'm not anymore...
但现在不是了
Somebody's pulling your string... Who is it?
有人惹了你，是谁？
No one...
没人
Not now...
至少现在没用
Never thought my skills from my former life would ever payoff...
从没想到当年学的本事还能用得上
CIA?
你是中情局的？
Well...
我想
that too...
算是吧
Come on, if I'm gonna die
如果我就要死了
I have the right to know my assassin a little better...
我有权知道是谁要杀我
I worked covert...
我曾经是
covert operations for the CIA...
中央情报局的特工
I was in China during Tiananmen Square,
六四天安门事件时，我在中国
Cuba, Panama, and I was in Columbia...
还去过古巴和巴拿马
when my daughter was killed...
当我身在哥伦比亚时 我的女儿被害了
This is Captain Hank Wilford...
我是卫尔福特队长
Could you tell us what this is about?
能告诉我们，这到底是怎么回事？
I don't want anyone else to die because they're talking to me...
乔，我不想任何和我谈话的人死去
So, what's it gonna be?
你说怎么办吧？
Huh-uh-uh...
不 不 不
It's your show, baby...
宝贝儿，你是主角
Just leave me out of this for now...
暂时别把我扯进来
There's a bomb in the hot dog cart!
在这个卖热狗的车上有炸弹
It's set to blow when my cell phone dies...
等我手机没电了，炸弹就会爆炸
In about 15 minutes...
差不多还有15分钟
I'm chained to the cart...
我被锁在车上了
What are the demands?
他有什么要求？
A public debate of the 2nd amendment...
一个对第二修正案的公开辩论
- Hmm... - Heard of it?
- 哼 - 听没听过？
Go, girl...
说的好
I'd like to understand,
我想知道
are there any other demands?
还有其他什么要求吗？
Can I come closer?
我能靠近些吗？
Any other demands?
有没用其他要求？
No...
没了
No!
没用了
Liberty,
丽柏蒂
I will kill anyone who comes close...
我会杀了任何想靠近你的人
We have no confirmation yet,
我们现在还不能确定
but it appears that KNBS reporter, Bill Tollman
但是记者比尔看起来
has been seriously hurt...
伤势严重
And that Liberty Wallace of McCloud Guns
麦克克劳德造枪厂的丽柏蒂 华莱士
is demanding a public debate about the constitution,
正在要求一个对宪法本身
and its role in our violent times...
和其影响的公开评论
She's grandstanding, got to be militia...
看起来像是个部队出身的
Sir...
长官
Yeah... Yes, sir...
是的长官
Yes, sir, Liberty Wallace...
是丽柏蒂 华莱士...
You were good under the pressure...
你表现的很好
And the whole world will applaud you...
全世界都会为你喝彩
Or laugh at me...
或者在笑我
The press is the least of my concerns at this point...
这时候媒体不是最要紧的
I'll try to move them back, but...
我会把他们都支开，但是...
Yes, sir... I'll move them back right away...
是长官 我马上把他们都轰走
Thank you, sir...
谢谢您，长官
Get rid of the press... Tell them it's a safety issue...
把媒体那些人都轰走 告诉他们是为他们安全着想
Uptown doesn't want this thing under a microscope...
上面不想此事再扩大了
They're gonna make a move, Joe...
乔，他们好像要行动了
They'll never disarm that bomb...
他们没机会拆炸弹的
They probably already guessed that...
他们自己也很清楚这点
You won't be alone in the final moment...
到了最后关头，你不会很孤单
Status on the theater?
戏院怎么样了？
Somebody welded all the side exits shut...
有人把所有出口都焊封了
We've got an entering team coming in,
我们想办法
- But the fire department... - Is stuck in traffic...
- 消防队呢？ - 交通堵塞，他们过不来
- All exits? - Yeah, our cutters won't work...
- 所有出口都焊了？ - 是，我们怎么也打不开
The only exit is onto the street, and through the front door...
所剩唯一的出口，就是前门入口处
So in effect they're hostages...
所以那些观众也都算是人质了
Tell me about your daughter again...
再跟我讲讲你女儿出事经过
A boy at school put a gun to her head,
一个男孩，拿枪对着她的头
and asked her
问她
if she believed in God...
是否相信上帝
What did she say?
她怎么回答的？
I don't know...
我不知道
Is that robot ready to go?
那个机器能用了吗？
It'll be here in 15...
15分钟就好
Wilford: What about the bomb truck?
防炸车在哪？
We've got one coming in from the 48... ETA... 30 minutes...
有一辆正在路上， 大概30分钟后到
General evacuation?
大概疏散情况
We've got a full retreat going...
我们正全力解决
We'll find this son of a bitch... It'll just take a little time...
终究会找到这个王八蛋的 只不过还需要一些时间
Tell me about your father...
聊聊你父亲
My father...
我父亲
He was my hero...
是我心目中的英雄
He was...
他是
After he...
在他
you know...
去世后
I had to leave school to earn a living...
我被迫退学，养活自己
One thing led to the next...
事情接踵而来
I found my self working in the family business
我进入父亲的公司工作时
that was no longer family-owned...
公司也已不属于我们家了
Captain, I've only got 10 guys...
队长，我只有这10个队员
We should be fine once the 53 squad shows up...
等53队到了就可以行动了
That should be another 10 or 12 minutes...
那还要等10-12分钟
We're not gonna make it...
恐怕没那么多时间了
It's all I knew... Along came Victor,
我只知道这些了 然后我认识了维克托
he was brilliant, thought he could save my father's company...
他很精明，我本以为父亲的企业有救了
Our first big deal was with the Saudis...
第一庄生意是和沙特
But the Iraqis were shooting us with our own guns...
但伊拉克用我们造的枪来打我们
What do people think the government does with all those used weapons?
知道政府怎样处理不用的武器吗？
Melt them down? Make little sculptures out of them?
把它们都融化了，然后做成雕像？
Once we took the company international,
当我们公司进军国际市场
suddenly we were in a different league...
突然间所有事
It got complicated...
都变得很复杂了
Here I am...
所以我现在会在这儿
And Russell made you feel human again...
拉塞尔让你变得又有人情味了
And anonymous...
还可以不张扬
You know, my great-great-grandfather,
跟你说，我的曾曾曾祖父
he designed the gun that changed the outcome of the Civil War...
设计出的枪改变了内战的结果
I grew up thinking that's what we were still doing...
我长大了还一直这么想
We are securing the building...
我们正在检查整座建筑
I'm really sorry about your daughter...
对你女儿的死我很遗憾
Joe...
乔
One less breathing to help us tell our story...
又少了一个知情人士
We've got the shooter on the roof of a building at 8...
发现有个枪手在楼顶
I don't care if it looks like the Russians,
我不管看起来像俄罗斯人
or the Pakistanis, or the Girl Scouts,
或是像巴基斯坦人， 还是童子军
that guy's voice is American...
那男的声音是个美国人
This is an internal thing, get on it...
这是内部的事 赶快...
I want to know who the fuck else is shooting at my wife...
我要知道还有谁在向我老婆开枪
Yeah...
什么事
Where are you going?
你上哪去？
Why?
干什么？
The bereaved husband...
真是个好丈夫
When are you gonna stop screwing around
你什么时候才可以
and tell me what this is all about?
告诉我这到底是怎么回事？
You're doing it by the book:
你完全是按书上说在做
go on a business trip:
先是出差
be unavailable for comment:
没人能联系到你对此事发表意见
touch down in Washington
到达华盛顿
for a little face time with the client:
跟客户见个面
check the temperature...
看看气温
I don't really have a whole lot of choice, now do I?
我现在是毫无选择
Joe...
乔
We know each other don't we?
我们都认识，对吧？
Don't we?
对吧？
You do any time in South America?
在南美洲坐过牢？
Well, who didn't?
有谁例外吗？
None of us really came through that
没一个出来后
with our mental health intact, did we?
心理没受到刺激的。
God knows, it took me a while
只有上帝才知道
to pull my shit together when I got back...
我花了多长时间才好些
Yeah...
没错
Yeah,
对啊
it's a mental health thing...
是精神上的刺激
You talk like a company man...
你谈话像个在公司上班的
Or at least, well, you were a company man,
至少你曾经是
because they'd never go for this kind of theatrical bullshit...
因为那些人说什么也不会做这样的蠢事
What is your beef with me?
你跟我有什么冤仇？
That you'd run away and let them take Liberty...
你撇下丽柏蒂，自己跑了
That you're not man enough to stand up for your wife...
你不算是个男人
Hope you're impressed with your life...
希望你对你的人生自豪
Grace and 9th...
去现场
- Sure about that, sir? - Grace and 9th!
- 您确定？ - 去现场
You've got it...
你说了算
- Shooter's still out here... - Shit, take cover fast...
- 枪手还在 - 快躲起来
The sniper is shooting at our guys on the ground...
那个狙击手在袭击我方地面上的队员
How many down?
有死伤吗？
No report yet...
暂时还没用
Over headset: Luke, it's Mac... We have the shooter...
我们抓到枪手了
We've got the guyon the roof...
楼顶的人已经抓到了
Nobody moves until we get more information... Understood?
没有新的情报，谁都别轻举妄动
Hail Mary, full of grace,
慈母慈爱
the Lord is with thee,
上帝与你同在
blessed art thou amongst women,
保佑你
blessed is the fruit of thy womb Jesus...
保佑耶稣
Looks like we've got a problem up here...
这里有点麻烦
It's not the sniper...
抓到的不是狙击手
Well, who the fuck is he? Why is he shooting?
那他是谁？ 为什么打枪？
No report yet...
还没有报告
...pray for us sinners, now and at the hour of our death...
为我们有罪之人祈祷
Amen...
阿门
Chuck says he's talking the gold star clearance...
那人说他有金星许可证
CIA?
中央情报局的？
Jesus, get him down here if he's still breathing...
如果他还活着，快把他弄下来
Joe,
乔
what is enough?
还不够吗？
Are you begging for lives?
你求我不要再杀了？
Yes...
是的
Where are the shots coming from?
查到从哪开的枪？
My guys are thinking the brick, maybe the concrete...
我的人认为不是这栋砖楼，就是水泥的
I'm thinking higher than the...
我想应该在一个更高处
Way too much information... Status on backup?
太多了 后援在哪？
It's probably a hoax...
可能是骗人的
I think it has something to do with her husband...
我想和她丈夫有关
Russell's been playing with fire...
拉塞尔一直都在玩火
Now, don't be jealous, dear...
亲爱的，不要嫉妒
Woman: Oh, fuck off...
滚蛋吧
Victor knew your voice...
维克托 熟悉你的声音
Is this some kind of setup?
这是个陷阱？
Come on, now think hard and you'll get it all figured out...
好好想想，你一定会想通的
What the fuck do you mean, think?
你说让我想，想什么？
Come on, come clean...
快，都交代吧
You've taken my life, you owe me that much...
我的命在你手里，你应该跟我说
If I'm CIA or FBl,
如果我是中央情报局或联邦调查局的
then I went through all of this
我做的这些
because someone very high up wants a lot of visibility...
是因为某个高层官员要更多的能见度
Okay, okay, it was a stupid thought...
好了，好了 是个很愚蠢的想法
Look, you can't write this off to be some big conspiracy...
不可以认为这件事是个什么阴谋
That's gonna confuse the fuck out of all of them...
那才会让所有人跟迷惑不解
Think... Think about how you're doing on the scoreboard...
想想你做的怎么样
It's not like I woke up one day and said,
那也不是我哪天突发奇想
"Wow, it's great to be in the lethal weapons business..."
我要在做致命武器的生意
It's like the guyon the corner
就想路边卖报的一样
who sells newspapers, it's what I do...
我只是在做我的工作
- What else am I gonna do? - Be the boss!
- 还能让我干什么？ - 当老板啊
It's your life, isn't it?
人生是你自己把握的
If the idea was for me to see God,
如果是让我接受上帝
you've achieved it...
你已经完成任务了
I mean, I prayed, for Christ's sake...
我已经祈祷了
To the parking garage... Let's assemble in there... Let's go!
去停车场，到那再装。 快走
When my daughter was killed, my wife came apart...
我女儿被死后 我老婆也支持不住了
We met the parents of the kid who did it...
我们与那个男孩的家长见了面
His father...
他父亲
cried...
哭了
And he told us that he had taught his son
他对我们说
how to use a gun safely...
他教过他儿子怎样安全用枪
Never saw it coming...
真没想到
I wanted to kill that kid...
我真想把那小孩给杀了
Then I wanted to kill the father...
然后我在把孩子父亲给杀了
But...
但是
here I am instead...
我现在在这儿
I like you...
我喜欢你
This is no way to die...
我不想这样死
For us there's no other wayout...
没其它路可走了
I thought about this for a long time...
我计划了很久了
Bomb squad wants us to move further back...
爆破队想让我们向后撤
Captain, it's Victor Wallace on the line...
队长，维克托 华莱士的电话
Nobody move...
谁都别动
Victor, Hank here...
维克托, 我是翰克
Hank?
翰克？
Jesus Christ...
我的天哪
Hank: Do you know what this is about?
你知道这是怎么回事吗？
I was hoping you'd tell me...
我本以为你能告诉我呢
I don't believe you...
我不信你不知道
We found a guyon the roof shooting at her... He looked CIA...
我们在楼顶抓到一个枪手 好像是中央情报局的
- Did you get him? - No, somebody else shot him...
- 你找到的？ - 不是，有人把他打伤了。
The guy we've got is not the sniper or maybe he's one of them...
这个人不是那个狙击手 但可能是同夥
My ass is hanging out here, Victor...
维克托，你要帮我啊
I need you to tell me what's going on...
我要你告诉我是怎么回事
What's going on? We're dealing with a nutcase...
怎么回事？ 告诉你，那人是个疯子
That's what's going on...
就这么回事
Yeah, or terrorists buying time...
可能，或者恐怖份子在争取时间
It's only been half an hour and the press is still stacking up...
才过了半小时，就已经很多媒体了
I'm five minutes away...
我有5分钟就到
This action may be connected to the recent lawsuit
恐怕是跟最近的官司有关
filed by seven of the largest gunmakers,
7家造枪大厂
alleging that efforts by government to impose
指控政府的枪支管理
gun safety measures, amounts to a conspiracy
他们指控这是
that violates constitutional guarantees of free trade...
违反宪法规定的
Wallace's company, McCloud Guns,
华莱士 的公司和 麦克克劳德公司,
is at the center of this controversy
因为拒绝签署
by refusing to become signatory to any government proposal
政府更严厉的枪支管理提案
that legislates more controls...
而成为这次风波的主角
Man: Thanks for that breaking news...
谢谢刚刚的紧急新闻
Now on the international...
现在国际新闻
31 cities and countries have brought charges against
31个城市和国家已上告制造商
manufacturers claiming they're not doing enough
控告他们防范措施做的不够 没能更好的控制
to keep guns out of the hands of children and criminals...
使枪支落入孩子和犯罪分子手里
Apparently, Wallace is staging a high-stakes protest
看起来，华莱士恰恰正在对
against the very industry
使她家族扬名的产业
that made her family famous in America...
进行一次高代价的抗议
Back to you, Dennis...
报告完毕
We're in the final stretch, Liberty...
丽柏蒂 我们已经到了最后时刻了
So,
那么
what's your plan?
你打算怎么办？
I don't want to die...
我不想死
I don't want anyone else to die because of me, Joe...
乔，我不希望其他人因我而死
Me neither...
我也不想
You know,
你要知道
the NRA is just gonna spin this and say it's because
枪支协会会说正因为有像你这样的人
of people like you that we need to be armed...
大家才需要有枪
Well, I was an honest law-abiding citizen...
我曾经也是遵纪守法的公民
By that definition I deserve to be armed...
那么说我也可以有枪
And I was acting out against the oppression
而我是为我们的自由
of our freedom...
才有次行为
There it is...
是这样的...
You know, I first saw you in Jerusalem...
我第一次见到你是在耶路撒冷
About three years ago...
大约三年前
You must have made a hell of a deal...
你肯定做了桩大买卖
'Cause they were kissing your ass...
因为他们对你很殷勤
- Did I meet you? - Nope...
- 我见到你了吗？ - 没有
I did business with Victor, though...
但是我替沙特阿拉伯
On behalf of the Saudis...
和维克托做过生意
It seems he likes to sell on all sides...
他好像有买主就卖
We met in our early days...
我们很久前就认识了
Seriously flawed mission to Columbia...
是在一次去哥伦比亚的任务
I saved his life...
我救过他的命
How funny...
多可笑
I saved the life of the man that killed my daughter...
我救了我女儿的凶手
Joe...
乔
Thanks, Barry...
谢谢你
I don't feel good about this...
我有种不详之感
Death isn't as ex citing as I thought it would be...
死亡没有我想的那样令人兴奋
Ex cuse me, please...
对不起...
Ex cuse me...
劳驾...
Ex cuse me, I'm Victor Wallace...
让一下, 我是维克托 华莱士...
Sir, you can't come through here...
先生你不能从这过
I'm the husband, you fucking moron...
我是那个人质的丈夫 你这个蠢货
Woman: Sir, just one question!
先生我有个问题
Don't talk to me...
别跟我讲话
Has this played into McCloud's position
此事会不会改变
on gun safety legislation?
麦克克劳德公司对枪支安全提案的立场？
This has absolutely nothing to do with McCloud Industries...
此事与公司无关
These are the actions of an insane man...
这事全是由一个疯子而起
And my wife is a wonderful woman...
我的太太是个非常好的女人
She's a wonderful woman...
是个非常好的女人
- Victor, you can't go out there... - I just want to let her see me...
- 你不能过去 - 我要让她知道我来了
Why?
为什么？
'Cause I think I know who this guy is...
我想我知道枪手是谁
And I think I can get her out of this...
我应该可以救我太太
Whatever you're thinking,
不管你怎么想的
- I can't let... - This is my problem...
- 我不能... - 这是我的事
Don't make me make problems for you...
别让我找你麻烦
Be good to the car...
别碰那推车
I said the car...
我是说推车
Liberty!
丽柏蒂!
Victor...
维克托...
Hey, Alex...
艾力克斯 你好
Well, here we are again,
我已经来了
in the kill zone... What can I do for you?
在你射程之内 我能做些什么？
I remember the day you wept like a baby
我还记得你那次你哭得像个孩子
while I promised not to let you die...
然后我跟你讲我不会让你死
Okay, okay, you saved my life, yeah...
对，对，你是救过我的命
Wasn't I thankful enough then?
我当初没有谢够吗？
Well, thanks again...
那我再谢你一次
I mean it...
我是真心的
- Victor... - But I have a feeling that...
- 维克托... - 但是我感觉到
what's really expected of me
你是想让我
is some sort of big, public confession...
当众忏悔什么
Am I right? What am I supposed to say?
我说的对吧 那我应该忏悔什么？
Joe, don't do it...
乔，别杀他
That...
难道说
that really shiny one that I have is actually for...
我得的那枚奖章
for leading a bunch of men to their death?
是因为我害了很多人？
Is that what I'm supposed to say?
我是要说这个吗？
Come on...
你知道的
Alex, it's a war...
这是场战争
That's the kind of stuff that happens...
死伤是难免的
You think I'm proud of it? I didn't ask for the medal...
你以为我以此为自豪？ 我没有要那枚奖章
Your death is gonna mean something...
你的死还有些意义
But my daughter's...
但我女儿的死
won't...
却没有
Joe, don't do it...
乔，别打了
Don't do it!
别杀他
- Don't! - Christ, he's been hit...
- 不要啊！ - 天啊，他被击中了
Get him out of here!
快把他救过来
Get him inside fast!
快点
Come on, pick him up! Move!
抬起他，快走
Let's go! Let's go!
快快快
Don't!
不要杀了
Liberty...
丽柏蒂...
Liberty!
丽柏蒂!
- It's time... - What?
- 到时候了 - 说什么？
Time for you to go...
你可以走了
The keys for your cuffs
手铐的钥匙
is in a box taped to the underside of the cart near the corner...
就在车角处一个盒子里
Okay, guys, it's got to be this one right here, 7th and Alvarado...
他肯定在这栋楼里
Move on it! 7th and Alvarado!
快行动 去这楼
Aah!
啊
Bring the chopper into the back,
快让直升机飞开
or this guy will blow it out of the sky...
否则枪手会把它打下来
Must be some kind of shooter if he's holed up that far...
他一定是个有经验的枪手
In the theater, officer needs backup...
戏院里需要更多人手帮忙
There's people panicking... Smoke everywhere...
戏院里人人惊慌 到处都是烟雾
A fire's been set or something...
好像是起火了
Hey!
嘿
Stop! Get away!
停下，别过去
There's a bomb!
那里有炸弹
Guys, all eyes out for the Wallace woman...
所有队员看住那个华莱士女士
Run! Run! There's a bomb!
快跑 快跑啊 有炸弹
Run!
快跑啊
Liberty,
丽柏蒂
it's up to you now...
现在看你的了
Time to choose...
做出选择吧
Everybody, move!
所有人快走
Computer: Video attachment is streaming...
播放录像
Senator Libby took at least three payments in cash...
参议员 利比 收了至少3次现金付款
Senator Lipton, Crick, Congressman Gomez,
参议员 利普顿,和 克里克, 国会议员 宫...
check Geneva bank accounts...
去查日内瓦银行帐户
You'll all be able to return to your cars,
等我们检查好了
once we secure the area...
大家就可以走了
Where's Russell?
罗索在哪里？
- Where's Russell? - I haven't seen him...
- 罗索他在哪里？ - 没见到他
Russell!
罗索
Get out of here!
快离开这儿
Don't!
不要进来
There's a bomb!
快离开 这里有炸弹
Get out! Run!
快走啊
Get out of here!
快走
The file with the video attachment has been sent...
录像已经寄出
As you can see, the area has been contained...
你们已经看到了
The situation is under control...
我们已经控制住了局面
Now, if you'll ex cuse me...
现在我要离开一下
All right, everybody into the alley, now!
所有人快进胡同儿
All right, get the fire hose...
快救火
Find that motherfucker!
把那个王八蛋给我找出来
No, sir...
没有的，长官
No other civilian casualties from the explosion...
爆炸没造成如何伤亡
We've had a fire reported in the back of the theater, sir...
队长，戏院后方着火了
No damage... No casualties... All noise and smoke...
没有任何伤亡
He made me shoot it...
是他让我
Close range...
在旁边开枪的
- Who are you? - I was looking for my wife's purse...
- 你是干什么的？ - 我在找我老婆的钱包
It's not safe in here... Get out of here...
这里很不安全 快离开
My great-great-grandfather,
我的曾曾祖父设计的枪
he designed the gun that changed the outcome of the Civil War...
改变了内战的结果
Where exactly were you when the first explosion took place?
在炸弹爆炸时，你在哪？
Umm... that's funny that you would ask...
我当时是...
Ex cuse me... Mr... Perry! Mr... Perry!
抱歉 派瑞先生，派瑞先生
I grew up thinking that's what we were still doing...
我长大了还是怎么想的
On the other side!
去另外一边
I'm really sorry about your daughter...
我很遗憾你女儿死了
My father...
我父亲
he was my hero...
他是我心目中的英雄
He was...
他是
Let me do what I can really do...
让我做我能做到的
Let me work from the inside... I can...
让我从内部调查
I can do something...
我能行的
Joe, I can really change things...
乔，我真的能行
I promise you I'll do it...
我保证我一定做
I promise...
我保证